That's it, Klara. We hope you like it.
就是这些, Klara. 我们希望你会喜欢.
Wonderful. Thank you. I love what you've done.
好极了. 谢谢你们. 我喜欢你们所做的一切.
Now there are a few things I've been thinking about.
不过有几桩事情我一直在考虑.
Some of my original ideas were not quite right.
我起初的一些想法并不十分正确.
For instance,
比方说,
the library as a gentlemen's club?
书房像绅士俱乐部那样?
I don't like that anymore.
我现在认为那样不行.
And the hallway furniture will have to change.
而且门厅的家具必须换掉.
The guest room, the maids' rooms, Antonio's dressing room...
客人的房间, 女佣的房间, Antonio的梳妆室...
And this color scheme strikes me as a little dull.
还有, 这种色调组合让我觉得有些单调.
Antonio's suggestion is to paint this...
Antonio建议把这个漆一下...
Now I know that today alone I have handed you two months' of work.
我知道单是今大我已经给了你们两个月的工作量.
But I do so want to stay on our original schedule.
但我还是希望遵循我们原定的时间安排.
Could you come back in a few weeks?
你们能几个星期后再来吗?
No problem!
没问题!